Dolev Binness

Software Developer

Full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience in Software Development as part of a large-scale company.

As part of my Recent work, I developed new features, worked constantly with clients and guided new employee.

I used technologies such as JavaScript, React, Redux, HTML and CSS along with Backend technologies such as Node.js.

Experience

2020 - 2023

Software Developer Amdocs

- Developed frontend and backend features as part of two teams.
- Chosen to work as part of a special-created team on a crucial new feature request from a major client.
- Planned and designed new features with product and UX/UI designers.
- Guided and taught all new developers of the UI team.
- Used newest technologies and programming languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux, CSS, RESTful API and Node.js.
- Familiarity with CI/CD workflows.
- Worked in an agile development environment.

2012 -2016

Logistics Officer (Lieutenant) IDF

- Managed a large-scaled constructions project as part of "IDF to the south" program including managing costs, schedule and performance.
- Chosen by the Logistics Corps to train and teach logistics cadets by applying variety of instructional techniques, including hands-on curriculum.
- Managed functional areas of logistics at the Paratroopers
 Brigade such as maintenance, transportation and supply

Contact

Phone

052-3462569

E-mail

dolevb13@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/dolev-binness/

Education

2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc):

Computer Science

IDC Herzliya - Israel

- Graduated with GPA of 88.
- Studied as part of a scholarship for excellence.
- Minored in Business
 Administration.

Skills

Frontend Technologies:

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, CSS

Backend Languages: Node.js,

Java

Other: Git, RESTful API, Bitbucket, Jenkins, MongoDB (NoSQL), Webpack